Contact

mbfindley0659@eagle.fgcu.ed

www.linkedin.com/in/ mariabelenfindley (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SAP Sales & Distribution
Business Development
Interpersonal Communication

Languages

Italian (Elementary)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)
English (Native or Bilingual)
Portuguese (Limited Working)

Certifications

Al Foundations
Personal Insurance
Sales Fundamentals
Microsoft Office Specialist: Microsoft
Office

Honors-Awards

Spire National Honor Society
Dean's List
Dean's List
Presidential Scholarship
President's List

Maria Belen Findley

Finance Student at FGCU- Class of 2024

Fort Myers, Florida, United States

Summary

Good financial management is essential and effective for people's and organization's financial health and long-term success.

My professional career is extensive in listening to the voice of the customer. I have spent 10+ years in customer service. I have managed complex business situations, including critical financial advisory. I excel when working in business environments that need to solve financial problems.

My experience has formed my character and allowed me to demonstrate my core capabilities:

Organization, persistence, resilience, relationship management, and critical thinking describe me the best.

I am passionate about how financial decisions impact lives and longterm business results.

My three-year plan includes becoming a financial advisor for highprofile clients. My education at FGCU will prepare me for a long career in helping people manage their money successfully.

Today, I am interested in contributing to roles related to financial advisory, financial planning, finance operations, and risk management. Helping others achieve their financial freedom.

Experience

The Club at Grandezza
Customer Service Representative
December 2019 - Present (3 years 6 months)
Estero, Florida, United States

I am passionate about customer service and eager to share my knowledge with the world. As a detail-oriented person who loves to help others, I have always gone out of my way to help my customers. I ensure customers are happy with their experience and will leave feeling satisfied. I use my customer service skills to find and resolve issues efficiently.

McCann

Translation Specialist
January 2016 - Present (7 years 5 months)

I employ my talent for languages and my international background to review hiring paperwork, hiring interviews, worldwide commercials scripts, and brand launches.

I have worked with multinational companies as customers, such as Nike, Nestle, Donofrio, Coke, Starbucks, Corona, and Adidas, with projects that require a pristine translation.

Education

Florida Gulf Coast University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Finance · (January 2023 - December 2024)

Florida SouthWestern State College
Associate of Arts - AA, Business Administration, Management and
Operations · (January 2020 - December 2022)